<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Pulse</string>
    <string name="heart">M25.119,2.564c12.434,0.023,18.68,5.892,24.88,17.612  c6.2-11.721,12.446-17.589,24.877-17.612c13.81-0.025,25.035,10.575,25.061,23.66c0.033,23.708-24.952,47.46-49.938,71.212  C25.016,73.685,0.03,49.932,0.064,26.224C0.085,13.14,11.309,2.539,25.119,2.564z</string>
    <string name="first_top_text">Start by taking deep breaths. Direct your focus to your breathing, slowly, in and out.</string>
    <string name="second_top_text">What seems to be bothering you today?</string>
    <string name="button1">People problems</string>
    <string name="q1button2">Managing Emotions</string>
    <string name="q1button3">Dealing with Stress</string>
    <string name="distressTop">A stable mind in the face of distress is essential in working through stressful situations. Distress tolerance entails how we can tolerate stress and pain in particularly challenging times, and deal with these challenges with a steady head.</string>
    <string name="distressBottom">Please, take a few seconds to think to yourself: What is the problem or situation you are facing?  Try to identify and describe the part of the situation that is difficult for you to accept.</string>
    <string name="distress2">Please think critically about the objective reality of the situation, not a worst-case or desired interpretation. Now, consider what causes led to this current situation; including consideration of those outside of your control.</string>
    <string name="distress3">Finally, remind yourself of the impermanence of the situation, and accept it for how it is. Without dismissing the reality, visualize yourself putting the crisis behind you. \n Practice radical acceptance of the current state of affairs, and know that you will move past it.</string>
    <string name="interpersonalTop">Many problems in daily life can arise from how we interact with those around us. Interpersonal effectiveness includes developing strategies we can use in dealing with social conflict, asking for what we need, and saying no when we need to.</string>
    <string name="interpersonalBottom">Dealing with others is complex, but we can start making our interactions more effective with DEAR strategies. D is for Describe: use explicit, descriptive language to describe your wants and needs.  Be specific about what you would like to be done.</string>
    <string name="interpersonal2">E is for Express. One of the biggest sources of interpersonal conflict is misunderstanding. Make sure to clearly express how situations make you feel, instead of expecting others to automatically understand your emotions.  Similarly, make sure to Assert: being direct about what you need to say. \n Avoid unnecessary vagueness and uncertainty in your language, and state clearly what you mean. </string>
    <string name="interpersonal3">Finally, don’t forget to Reinforce. If those around you behave in ways you appreciate, offer them positive feedback so they understand your appreciation. Thanking others and small friendly gestures can go a long way in building healthy and mutually-beneficial interpersonal relationships. \n Remember DEAR: Describe, Express, Assert, Reinforce.</string>
    <string name="emotionTop">Being in touch with our emotions is very important for mental health, but we must be careful that our emotions don’t take over our actions at inappropriate times. Emotional regulation consists of learning how we can change emotions that we want to change in ourselves.</string>
    <string name="emotionBottom">We can use STOPP to help regulate our emotions. We’ve already Stopped, and Taken a breath. Next is Observe. Take a few seconds, and ask yourself—what thoughts and emotions are on your mind? What are you focusing on?</string>
    <string name="emotion2">Next is Pull Back: put some perspective. Try to take a step back and think about the bigger picture, and of another way you might consider the situation in a more positive light. Once you’ve done that, think about how important it is on a larger scale—whether you should let it have such an impact on you right now.</string>
    <string name="emotion3">Finally in STOPP, Proceed. With your reframed perspective, think critically about the best course of action for the yourself, others, and the situation. Keep in mind your values, how you will feel about your actions, and what appropriate courses of action you think could be effective. \n Remember STOPP: Stop, Take a Breath, Observe, Pull Back, Proceed.</string>
    <string name="finishButton">Finish</string>
</resources>
